# Chandra Kumar N

Business Analyst/ Quality Engineer/Release Management



+919739979118



ckumarnagesh0087@gmail.com



Bengaluru, Karnataka

# ılıl Skills

- Requirement Gathering
- Risk Management
- **Business Planning**
- **Quality Analysis**
- Agile Project Management
- **Project Management**
- Forecasting
- Scrum
- Strategic Planning
- Team Building & Leadership



# **Summary**

Seasoned professional, with proven 15 years of progressive and diverse IT product development and Operation experience. Skilled in Strategic Business Planning, Risk Management, Business Development, provide creative solutions to complex problems, Change Management, Business Process Improvements. Target assignments in Agile Scrum Project Management with proven strategy skills. Businessrequirement elicitation and converting user requirements to functional requirements, proposing solution in Agile environment.



#### Education

## **ICFAI** University

MBA in Finance



# **Experience**

#### Ab in Bev

Business Analyst/ Quality Engineer/Release Management

- Supported in house application "Click and Guru" in various squads such as Basic, Leave and Absence and Separation as a Specialist - Quality Analyst Technology And Business Analyst.
- Played multiple roles as Business Analyst, Quality Analyst for One Stop Shop, Live Chat and Email2case successfully and had successful completion of OSS implementation for Click application.
- Conducting meetings with Product owner and the Stakeholders to get the requirements.
- Conducting the Sprint Planning and Refinement meetings with the team.
- Sprint goal and prioritization and continuous User Story refinement from the backlog.
- Conducting daily scrum meeting with the team.
- Took the ownership for OSS Squad for Click work towards timely and successfully delivered user stories.
- Complete the assistance during UAT phase through the Demo.
- Define improvement action, process action for the process.
- Adapted the new methodology Agile way of working with continuous grooming and reduction in sprint from 5-4 weeks by creating backlogs to 2 weeks.
- Co-ordinating with the Release management team and making the arrangements for the release.
- Conducting Monthly bugs analysis with the team.
- Currently working as Test Coordinator for Salesforce to Servicenow Migration.
- Updating the testing status to Business daily
- Experienced in Agile Methodologies like Scum, Pokering Grooming, Sprint.
- Creation of new scenarios based on the functionality and adding cases to the existing scenarios according to new requirements.
- Strongly involved in Defects Reporting, Defects Classification, Defects Tracking and Defects Closing using Azure Devops.
- Supporting the development team for issues and resolution of defects.
- Performing the RCAs for all the bugs.
- Performing the Ad hoc testing to identify the bugs.

- Regression testing for every sprints.
- Preparing the training deck to Business UAT tester.
- Provide training to Business on the UAT testing.
- Manual testing (Servicenow, Salesforce, SAP Testing).

#### **Accenture**

Team Lead

Oct 2015 - Feb 2018

- Allocating work to the team
- Handling the queries
- Credit card creations
- Credit card blocks and unblocks
- Reconciliations
- Interacting with EBM and VP once in month.
- Attending Monthly reviews with Global Directors
- Preparing the dashboards
- Preparing the Metrics and report to the clients

### Infosys

**Process Lead** 

Sep 2013 - Oct 2015

- Capitalization of assets through asset module and inventory module
- Calculation of DD&A
- Inventory period open and close
- FA vs GL Reconciliation
- Inventory vs GL Reconciliation
- CWIP vs GL Reconciliation
- Depreciation Reconciliation
- PPE Schedules

## **IBM Global Process services**

Senior F&A Executive

Oct 2009 - Sep 2013

- Bank Accounts
- Unapplied Cash Accounts
- Contingent and Liability
- Fixed Assets Reconciliations